development: &non_production_settings
  api_key: 8u5ixtdnq9csc84cok0owswgo
  # bcrypt can be used to encrypt valid possible answers in your session; http://bcrypt-ruby.rubyforge.org/
  # (recommended if you are using cookie session storage)
  # NOTE: bcrypt_salt must be a valid bcrypt salt; for security PLEASE CHANGE THIS, open irb and enter; require 'bcrypt'; BCrypt::Engine.generate_salt
  bcrypt_salt: $2a$10$j0bmycH.SVfD1b5mpEGPpe
  # an optional logarithmic var which determines how computational expensive the hash is to calculate (a cost of 4 is twice as much work as a cost of 3)
  bcrypt_cost: 10 # default is 10, must be > 4 (large number means slower encryption)
  # if you'd rather NOT use bcrypt, just remove these two settings, bcrypt_salt and bcrypt_cost, valid possible answers will be MD5 digested in your session
  questions:
      - question: 'Лёд холоден или горяч?'
        answers: 'холоден,холодный'
      - question: 'Какого цвета апельсин?'
        answers: 'оранжевый'
      - question: 'Сколько будет два прибавить 3?'
        answers: '5,пять'
      - question: 'Сколько будет 5-ю два?'
        answers: '10,десять'
      - question: 'Сколько перечислено цветов в списке: зеленый, коричневый, говяжий and голубой?'
        answers: '3,три'
      - question: 'Как зовут Мишу?'
        answers: 'миша,михаил'
      - question: '11 вычесть 1?'
        answers: '10,десять'
      - question: 'Горяча или холодна кипящая вода?'
        answers: 'горяча,горячая'
      - question: 'Какого сегодня цвета моя синяя футболка?'
        answers: 'синего,синяя'
      - question: 'Сколько будет 16 прибавить 4?'
        answers: '20,двадцать'

test:
  *non_production_settings

production:
  *non_production_settings